Hilda Mason, Statehood Party 135
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 1
  - DC Women's Political Caucus Endorsement Policy and Caucus Info, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Model State Constitution, undated (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Mason New Release, 6 August 1981 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Home Rule Study Memo, 5 March 1990 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - "Greater Washington Area Population" Washington Post, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Report on Bill 7-154, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Amendment to H.R 51 re: Condition: voters delete sec. 1110 committeee Mark-up, 2 June 1987 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - An Amendment to the Committee Print Offered by Mr. Combest of Texas, undated (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Fiscal Prospects of the State of New Columbia, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Fauntroy Responses and Remarks, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - D.C Statehood Convention Delegates Addresses, undated (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Committee Print: H.R 51 Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Statehood Mark-up, 19 May 1987 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Substitute to the Committee Print of Bill 8-488 Representatives and Senators terms of Office Compensation and Procurement Amendment Act, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Constitution of the State of New Columbia, 29 May 1982 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Constitution for the State of New Columbia Approval Act, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - H.R 1629 and H.R 51, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - 1984 Statehood Memos (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - 1990 Memos and Reports (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Mount Zion United Methodist Church, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Sumner School, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Statehood Clippings 1987 1 of 2 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Statehood Clippings 1987 2 of 2 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Statehood Clippings, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Statehood Clippings 1988 1 of 2 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Statehood Clippings 1988 2 of 2 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Julius Hobson Info 1 of 3, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Julius Hobson Info 2 of 3, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Julius Hobson Info 3 of 3, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Dennis Sobin for D.C City Council, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - "A Legislator with Statehood on His Mind "NY Times, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Faith For U.S Representatives, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Mt. Zion Cemetery, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Briefing Book from H.R 51, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Democarcy, Federalism and the Governance of the Nation's Captial, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Testimony from March 5 1993 Budget Hearing (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Constitution of the State of New Columbia, 29 May 1982 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - "Fiscal Propects for the State of New Columbia" Report by Brimmer & Company Inc., 1986 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Home Rule Act as Amended, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Hearing and Markup Before House of Representations, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - H.R 3861, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - " A Decade of Home Rule: The Challenge Continues", 1985 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - New House Rule Notes (typed), undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - State of the District Address '85, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Self- Determination Budget Hearing, 22 February 1994 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Self-Determination Budget Mark-up, 11 March 1994 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Self-Determination Budget Mark-up, 28 April 1993 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Committee on Self-Determination, 18 April 1994 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Self-Determination, 28 April 1993 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Committee on Self-Determination Public Hearing, 28 April 1993 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Statehood Const. Conv Budg. '85 Req, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Committee on Self-Determination Committee Meeting, 4 February 1993 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Committee on Self-Determination Budget Hearing, 5 March 1993 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Committee on Self-Determination Budget Mark-up, 12 March 1993 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Committee on Self-Determination, 5 March 1993 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Committee on Self-Determination Budget Mark-up, 12 March 1993 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Committee on Self Determination, 5 November 1992 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Committee on Self-Determination, 4 June 1992 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Committee on Self-Determination, 6 February 1992 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Committee on Regional Authority Regular Committee Meeting, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Committee on Self-Determination, February 1993 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Committee on Judiciary and Education Mark-up Meeting, 5 August 1993 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Mark-up H.R 51- D.C Statehood Bill, 5 August 1993 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Statehood Commission Amendment Act of 1994 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Bill 7-154 Constitution for the State of New Columbia Approval Act, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Building Safer Communities with our Youth: Preventing Crime and Drug Abuse, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - H.R 3861, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Constitutional Convention Minute Request, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Copies of Correspondence and Newspaper articles, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence to Supporters of self determination, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Council of the District of Columbia Notice D.C Law 3-171, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Statehood Constitutional Convention Initiative of 1979 Bill, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - The Plan for Judicial System autonomy for the District of Columbia, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Statehood 1 of 4, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Statehood 2 of 4, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Statehood 3 of 4, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Statehood 4 of 4, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Statehood Constitutional Convention and After 1 of 2, 1982-1985 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Statehood Constitutional Convention and After 2 of 2, 1982-1985 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - The Briefing Book for H.R 51 The D.C Statehood Bill, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Statehood Party ACCC 99-30, 1971-1994 (Box 20, Folder 1)